<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:dam="http://www.day.com/dam/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
    jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:referenceable,mix:versionable]"
    jcr:primaryType="dam:Asset"
    jcr:uuid="0ee10581-9c46-4506-8719-df4371f6f36a">
    <jcr:content
        cq:name="adobe-is-a-leader-in-2021-forrester-agile-cms-wave"
        cq:parentPath="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/blogposts"
        jcr:description=""
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:16:10.843+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        jcr:primaryType="dam:AssetContent"
        jcr:title="Adobe is a leader in 2021 Forrester Agile CMS Wave"
        contentFragment="{Boolean}true"
        lastFragmentSave="{Date}2021-03-03T16:16:10.843+01:00">
        <data
            cq:model="/conf/blog-demo/settings/dam/cfm/models/blogpost"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <master
                cq:tags="[blog-tags:news,blog-tags:experience-cloud,blog-tags:experience-manager,blog-tags:creative-cloud]"
                jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                categories="[blog-tags:news,blog-tags:creative-cloud,blog-tags:experience-cloud,blog-tags:experience-manager]"
                categories_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:44.125+01:00"
                content="&lt;p>Today Forrester Research, an independent analyst firm, rated Adobe a leader in The Forrester Wave™: Agile Content Management Systems (CMSes), Q1 2021. Adobe Experience Manager was one of 15 solutions evaluated across 26 criteria, grouped into three main categories: current offering, strategy, and market presence.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>We are honored to be positioned as a leader with the highest scores in the current offering and strategy categories. We also tied for the highest score in the market presence category. In addition, Adobe received the highest scores among all participating vendors in the community and market approach criteria.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>We believe being rated a leader reflects the success of our customers and partners, who are delivering digital experiences that delight their customers, employees and partners. Our vision and strategy for agile CMS is simple: build a content system that provides IT, developers, and marketing organizations agility to deliver exceptional experiences. This means the system should be:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>Able to handle diverse content types and formats that form the basis of immersive experiences.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Focused on increasing velocity through the content journey — from ideation, creation, and through to delivery.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Able to manage headless, head-on and hybrid content implementation that scales content access horizontally and vertically.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Intelligent — able to measure content performance across all aspects of the journey.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;p>In&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager.html&quot;>Adobe Experience Manager&lt;/a>, we realize this vision with a cloud-native content management system that makes it easier for any sized brand — enterprise, mid-market, or an organization — to deliver exceptional experiences, across every touchpoint.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Omnichannel experiences&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Adobe is laser focused on providing brands with the most powerful and flexible tools for omnichannel content management. This means meeting customer’s rising expectations for app-like experiences across any surface. However, what is evolving is that now everyone owns the experiences — marketers, frontend developers, backend developers, DevOps, and IT — they need tools to be agile; to go from ideation to creation to management to delivery of omnichannel experiences. Adobe Experience Manager is designed to empower all of these personas for efficient management of exceptional experiences everywhere.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Adobe Experience Manager allows developers to easily access headless content using our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-sites/graph-ql.html&quot;>GraphQL and RESTful APIs&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;to fuel experiences in Single Page Apps (SPAs), mobile apps, or IoT apps. GraphQL lets developers get exactly the content they need using fewer network requests which results in faster apps. Adobe Experience Manager also offers maximum enterprise flexibility to extend from&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager/headless-cms.html&quot;>headless&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;to hybrid content management as needed. Our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-sites/single-page-app-editing.html&quot;>SPA Editor&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;allows marketing to edit and preview client-side SPA content. This enables marketers and developers to better collaborate and manage modern front-end experiences with agility and flexibility. Adobe Experience Manager also allows marketers to re-use content to create traditional web experiences, using full&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-sites/in-context-editing.html&quot;>WYSIYWG editing&lt;/a>. And at the click of a button, transform any authored site into a Progressive Web App (PWA) for easy delivery of app-like mobile optimized experiences.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Experience intelligence for exceptional experiences at scale&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Customers want more relevant content, yet brands are struggling to deliver it. The explosion of touchpoints, formats and content make personalization hard to achieve with limited marketing resources. But to cut through the noise, brands need to deliver exceptional, personalized experiences at every touchpoint along the customer journey. This means intelligent optimization and personalization at every moment.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Adobe Experience Manager helps teams scale to meet this challenge with automation powered by machine learning (ML) and artificial intelligence (AI) across the creation, management and experience delivery phases. Intelligent services automate&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-assets/smart-tagging.html&quot;>tagging&lt;/a>,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-assets/smart-crop.html&quot;>cropping&lt;/a>,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-assets/asset-microservices.html&quot;>manipulating&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;and the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-assets/dynamic-media.html&quot;>optimized delivery&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;of content assets to improve marketer efficiency. Then AI-tailored experiences are delivered using A/B testing,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-sites/targeting-insights.html&quot;>targeting&lt;/a>, and personalization of content through native integrations with&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/target.html&quot;>Adobe Target&lt;/a>. Actionable cross-channel&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-sites/content-insights.html&quot;>insights&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;to understand customer behavior are easy to achieve with native&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/analytics/adobe-analytics.html&quot;>Adobe Analytics&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;instrumentation.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h2>“With the Adobe platform and the Adobe cloud, our maturity is growing very quickly in terms of the way we can consume and analyze data, advance personalization, manage site updates and improvements, and deliver an actionable and connected UX to optimize our resource management and enterprise investment,”&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.adobe.com/en/publish/2020/07/30/pentairs-recipe-for-digital-success-central-experience-management-and-a-data-centric-mindset.html#gs.tqanq4&quot;>Patrick Theimer&lt;/a>, vice president of digital customer at Pentair&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Agility and faster time to value for IT and marketers in the cloud&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>To succeed in today’s competitive digital-first landscape, brands need the agility to rapidly launch and iterate new digital experiences. Built on cloud-native architecture, Experience Manager provides flexibility to start small and grow with a brand’s varied experience management needs. Adobe Experience Manager’s container — and services-based architecture scales dynamically and is always current with the latest features, all of which removes the headache of constant upgrades and integration management.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h2>“Our clients operate in increasingly challenging times. They face geopolitical uncertainty, complex modern markets and an ever-changing regulatory environment. Moving our site to Adobe Experience Manager as a Cloud Service has given us the ability to experiment and explore more innovative ways to deliver the ideal digital experience and make a difference for our clients.”&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.adobe.com/en/publish/2020/10/19/how-cloud-accelerated-dechert-digital-experience.html#gs.t2tfsw&quot;>Alice Cervantes&lt;/a>, senior digital marketing manager at Dechert&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Our flexible cloud architecture is augmented by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://experienceleaguecommunities.adobe.com/t5/adobe-experience-manager/adobe-s-digital-foundation-blueprint-and-how-it-can-help-you-aem/td-p/369637&quot;>Digital Foundation Blueprint&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;best practices — insights distilled from thousands of successful go-lives, production-ready&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-sites/out-of-the-box-components.html&quot;>Core Components&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-sites/managed-cloud.html&quot;>flexible DevOps tools&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;— which allows brands to go live with new web and app experiences within days.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Adobe Experience Manager also accelerates enterprise content workflows starting with a single source of truth for content across the organization based in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-assets.html&quot;>rich enterprise digital asset management capabilities&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;including&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager-assets/adobe-asset-link.html&quot;>native connections to Adobe Creative Cloud&lt;/a>. And now with our recent&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.workfront.com/blog/adobe-completes-workfront-acquisition&quot;>acquisition of Workfront&lt;/a>, teams have best in class capabilities to efficiently orchestrate marketing workflows associated with experience delivery.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>With Adobe Experience Manager, we are honored to be helping many of the most innovative brands — mid-size, departmental, or enterprise — efficiently deliver differentiated digital experiences.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Download a complimentary copy of the full report&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/offer/the-forrester-wave-cms-2021.html?foo=abd&quot;>here&lt;/a>: The Forrester Wave: Agile Content Management Systems (CMSes), Q1 2021 or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/request-consultation/experience-cloud.html&quot;>contact us to see it in action.&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                content_x0040_ContentType="text/html"
                content_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:44.125+01:00"
                heroImage="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/blogposts/heroimage.png"
                heroImage_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:44.125+01:00"
                publishedAt="{Date}2021-02-23T16:15:00.000+01:00"
                publishedAt_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:44.124+01:00"
                publishedBy="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/authors/crosby-togwell"
                publishedBy_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:44.124+01:00"
                title="Adobe is a leader in 2021 Forrester Agile CMS Wave"
                title_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:44.124+01:00"/>
            <short
                cq:tags="[blog-tags:news,blog-tags:experience-cloud,blog-tags:experience-manager,blog-tags:creative-cloud]"
                jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                categories="[blog-tags:news,blog-tags:creative-cloud,blog-tags:experience-cloud,blog-tags:experience-manager]"
                categories_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:46.514+01:00"
                content=" We also tied for the highest score in the market presence category. Intelligent — able to measure content performance across all aspects of the journey. Adobe Experience Manager also offers maximum enterprise flexibility to extend from headless to hybrid content management as needed. Our SPA Editor allows marketing to edit and preview client-side SPA content. This enables marketers and developers to better collaborate and manage modern front-end experiences with agility and flexibility. The explosion of touchpoints, formats and content make personalization hard to achieve with limited marketing resources. This means intelligent optimization and personalization at every moment."
                content_x0040_ContentType="text/plain"
                content_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:16:10.814+01:00"
                heroImage="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/blogposts/heroimage.png"
                heroImage_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:46.514+01:00"
                publishedAt="{Date}2021-02-23T16:15:00.000+01:00"
                publishedAt_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:46.514+01:00"
                publishedBy="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/authors/crosby-togwell"
                publishedBy_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:46.513+01:00"
                title="Adobe is a leader in 2021 Forrester Agile CMS Wave"
                title_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:46.513+01:00"
                variationCreationDate="{Date}2021-03-03T16:15:46.513+01:00"/>
        </data>
        <metadata
            jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
        <model jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <variations jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <short
                    jcr:description=""
                    jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    jcr:title="Short"
                    name="short">
                    <properties
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        synchronizeWithVersion="[title:f8e8fbc2-8cec-4c24-9a84-06b42ef2a326,publishedBy:f8e8fbc2-8cec-4c24-9a84-06b42ef2a326,publishedAt:f8e8fbc2-8cec-4c24-9a84-06b42ef2a326,heroImage:f8e8fbc2-8cec-4c24-9a84-06b42ef2a326,content:f8e8fbc2-8cec-4c24-9a84-06b42ef2a326,categories:f8e8fbc2-8cec-4c24-9a84-06b42ef2a326]"/>
                </short>
            </variations>
        </model>
        <related jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
