<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:dam="http://www.day.com/dam/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
    jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:referenceable,mix:versionable]"
    jcr:primaryType="dam:Asset"
    jcr:uuid="75985870-b19c-4072-8ae2-feac7c54e982">
    <jcr:content
        cq:name="5-reasons-why-you-shouldn-t-miss-adobe-summit-this-year"
        cq:parentPath="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/blogposts"
        jcr:description=""
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:11:40.311+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        jcr:primaryType="dam:AssetContent"
        jcr:title="5 reasons why you shouldn’t miss Adobe Summit this year"
        contentFragment="{Boolean}true"
        lastFragmentSave="{Date}2021-03-03T16:11:40.311+01:00">
        <data
            cq:model="/conf/blog-demo/settings/dam/cfm/models/blogpost"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <master
                cq:tags="[blog-tags:news,blog-tags:experience-cloud,blog-tags:experience-manager,blog-tags:adobe-summit]"
                jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                categories="[blog-tags:news,blog-tags:adobe-summit,blog-tags:experience-cloud,blog-tags:experience-manager]"
                categories_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:10:37.867+01:00"
                content="&lt;p>Adobe Summit 2021 registration is off to a great start. Set for April 27 — 29, the virtual event will bring together Experience Makers from some of the world’s most-recognized brands. No matter where you are in your career, you’ll be able to attend sessions that will leave you and your company future-proof. This is true regardless of your area of expertise — from content creation and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title=&quot;personalization&quot; href=&quot;https://helpx.adobe.com/experience-manager/6-3/sites/administering/using/personalization.html&quot;>personalization&lt;/a>, to data and analytics.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;https://portal.adobe.com/pages/adobe/as21/signin&quot;>Register for free&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;to build the skills to create client experiences that inspire loyalty and drive growth.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Explore the latest customer experience trends&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>This year’s Adobe Summit comes at a time of seismic shifts in the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a title=&quot;customer experience&quot; href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/experience-cloud/customer-experience-management.html&quot;>customer experience&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;landscape. That’s why we’ve planned more than 250 sessions and training workshops that will highlight game-changing innovation in how brands deliver experiences at every stage of the customer journey.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“Driving demand during COVID is top-of-mind for a lot of businesses,” says Alexandra Quick, a product marketing manager at Adobe. “That’s a subject we’re attacking head-on with a dedicated session.” Overall, participants can expect a “huge emphasis on digital marketing,” she adds. Included within this emphasis will be a deep dive into all the ways companies are using new technologies to advance their mobile commerce capabilities.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“In the case of digital commerce, 2020 has been an incredible year for growth,” says Shannon Hane, senior product marketing manager for commerce at Adobe. This has been true on both the B2C and the B2B sides of industries. Adobe Summit 2021, she says, represents a unique opportunity to learn “how people are managing that growth and adapting their commerce capabilities and experiences to this new environment.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Get inspired by top brands from around the world&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>This year’s conference will represent one of the most industry-diverse entries in the Summit series to date, with speakers from every corner of the tech sector, as well as education, financial services, sports, retail, and more. Leaders from each industry will share the field notes they’ve amassed during the unprecedented upheaval of the last year. Among the subjects you can expect them to cover are the following:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/experience-platform.html&quot;>Adobe Experience Platform&lt;/a>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Analytics, Insights, and Activation&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>B2B Marketing and ABM&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Campaign Management&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Collaborative Work Management&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Content Creation&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Developer Ecosystem&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Digital Commerce&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Digital Document Productivity&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Personalization&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Trends and Inspiration&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;h3>Discover best practices and new techniques and products&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Maybe you’re a B2B company looking to sell directly to consumers, or a retailer looking to recreate the physical showroom experience online. Whatever your challenge, you’re likely to find a case study at this year’s Adobe Summit that offers you a shortcut to success in building customer experience, from IT to creative — and everything in between.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Finding and delighting customers takes more than the right strategy, however. It also requires the right tools, not to mention knowing how to use them. This April, you can expect to learn all about the latest in task-automation software, progressive web applications, 3D visualization, and more.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Customers will also get a sneak peek at the exciting new features coming to Adobe products, including&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/experience-manager.html&quot;>Adobe Experience Manager&lt;/a>&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.adobe.com/marketing/marketo.html&quot;>Marketo Engage&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“We’re going to showcase the innovations that we’re launching this year that give customers and brands the ability to make those experiences happen in a more agile, personalized way on every channel,” says product marketing manager Vebeka Guess.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Connect with Adobe experts and your peers worldwide&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Opportunities for connecting with other Experience Makers can be hard to come by these days. That’s why networking activities are included with your Summit registration. Just because this year’s Summit is virtual, doesn’t mean it can’t be interactive.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“It’s not just the content that draws people to Summit, but the ability to network and interact with experts at Adobe, and also your peers,” Vebeka says. “People come to Summit to learn from each other as well as from Adobe.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>To this end, we’ll be launching Braindate, an interactive networking platform that will enable you to engage and interact with Summit attendees, expanding your learning and your network.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>It’s free and it’s virtual&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Adobe Summit 2021 is the most accessible conference ever for Experience Makers around the globe, and represents a unique opportunity for those who haven’t always been able to join in person. Reserve your spot now for the world’s premier conference on customer experience, where you’ll learn how to drive demand in a rapidly shifting marketplace, explore the latest technological and strategic trends, and draw inspiration from experts who are changing the world — one customer experience at a time.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>Have questions? Visit our official Adobe Summit 2021&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://apps.enterprise.adobe.com/go/7015Y000002e5NKQAY&quot;>website&lt;/a>. You can also connect with us on social media using the hashtags #AdobeSummit, #MagentoImagine, or #MktgNation.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                content_x0040_ContentType="text/html"
                content_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:10:37.867+01:00"
                heroImage="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/blogposts/heroimage.png"
                heroImage_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:10:37.866+01:00"
                publishedAt="{Date}2021-02-16T16:10:00.000+01:00"
                publishedAt_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:10:37.866+01:00"
                publishedBy="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/authors/crosby-togwell"
                publishedBy_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:10:37.866+01:00"
                title="5 reasons why you shouldn’t miss Adobe Summit this year"
                title_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:10:37.866+01:00"/>
            <short
                cq:tags="[blog-tags:news,blog-tags:experience-cloud,blog-tags:experience-manager,blog-tags:adobe-summit]"
                jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                categories="[blog-tags:news,blog-tags:adobe-summit,blog-tags:experience-cloud,blog-tags:experience-manager]"
                categories_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:11:04.632+01:00"
                content="Adobe Summit 2021 registration is off to a great start. Register for free to build the skills to create client experiences that inspire loyalty and drive growth. “That’s a subject we’re attacking head-on with a dedicated session.” This has been true on both the B2C and the B2B sides of industries. Finding and delighting customers takes more than the right strategy, however. That’s why networking activities are included with your Summit registration. “People come to Summit to learn from each other as well as from Adobe.” Have questions? Visit our official Adobe Summit 2021 website."
                content_x0040_ContentType="text/plain"
                content_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:11:34.846+01:00"
                heroImage="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/blogposts/heroimage.png"
                heroImage_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:11:04.631+01:00"
                publishedAt="{Date}2021-02-16T16:10:00.000+01:00"
                publishedAt_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:11:04.631+01:00"
                publishedBy="/content/dam/blog-demo/en/authors/crosby-togwell"
                publishedBy_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:11:04.631+01:00"
                title="5 reasons why you shouldn’t miss Adobe Summit this year"
                title_x0040_LastModified="{Date}2021-03-03T16:11:04.631+01:00"
                variationCreationDate="{Date}2021-03-03T16:11:04.630+01:00"/>
        </data>
        <metadata
            jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
        <model jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
            <variations jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                <short
                    jcr:description=""
                    jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:Taggable]"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    jcr:title="Short"
                    name="short">
                    <properties
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        synchronizeWithVersion="[title:6add1ea5-9632-4ead-9330-583407191946,publishedBy:6add1ea5-9632-4ead-9330-583407191946,publishedAt:6add1ea5-9632-4ead-9330-583407191946,heroImage:6add1ea5-9632-4ead-9330-583407191946,content:6add1ea5-9632-4ead-9330-583407191946,categories:6add1ea5-9632-4ead-9330-583407191946]"/>
                </short>
            </variations>
        </model>
        <related jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
